Plan T Films Shane Nigam Films .
Anwar Rasheed Presents .
Mom ...
Grandma is awake .
Careful ...
- Vinu ... - Hmnn .
We 've to change her diaper .
Can 't we do this in the morning ?
Hold her .
Come ...
Alright .
There ... lift her from here .
Lift ... a bit more !
Got it ? Yeah ?
Amma , we can 't do this 4-5 times a day .
We need to make some arrangement .
- What arrangement ? - Let 's get a home nurse .
And who 'll pay for that ?
We can hardly meet ends on my salary .
A home nurse ... indeed !
Come and hold her .
Please hold her properly , Vinu !
Haven 't I been holding her properly all this while ?
Quickly , please !
If you are doing it half-heartedly , don 't do it .
Go back to bed .
' Revathi '
' Shane Nigam '
" The Past . "
It 's OK .
Isn 't it better than being bedridden ?
Be at peace that her passing is for the better .
[ CRYING ]
[ PRIYA CALLING ]
My mother
passed away recently .
It is since then
I have been feeling like this .
Why did you stop your medication ?
For a while
I had them as prescribed .
Later ...
When I recovered
I stopped taking them . - You shouldn 't stop like that .
The previous doctor here would have instructed you clearly , right ?
Asha , you have clinical depression .
It 's a disorder .
And it doesn 't get cured like flu .
You stopped your medication abruptly and hence
you are facing this issue now .
You need to continue your medication . Please don 't stop midway .
Is there anyone in your family
with a similar medical history ?
My mother ...
She was quick-tempered .
She 'd get really upset over silly things .
So
she clearly understood me .
Whatever the problem
I was able to share with her .
She was very supportive .
Later she had a stroke
and lost her memory .
Towards the end ...
She
even forgot my name .
Who else is there at home ?
I have a son .
He completed his D. Pharm
and is job hunting .
And is your son like you ?
Does he open up to his mother ?
He is not like me .
He is like his father .
Two pegs , please .
Vinu , will you be late ?
Hmm .
Give me a call when you 're free .
So what are Vinu 's plans now ?
What about his job hunt ?
He is still searching .
He got a couple of offers . But they were far from here .
So he rejected them .
He can go for them now .
If he gets something nearby , we can consider .
What is he going to get here ?
If you need any assistance , aren 't we all around ?
Let him go !
If he leaves , won 't I be by myself ?
Who else do I have ?
[ SOUNDS FROM THE TV ]
- Vinu ... - Hmm ?
Move the wheelchair to Grandma 's room .
I have cleaned it .
[ SOUNDS FROM THE TV ]
Didn 't I just ask you to move it ?
Shall we put this on OLX ( EBAY ) ?
It is just lying around here .
Just do as I ask !
[ SOUNDS FROM THE TV ]
Darn !
- What fell ? - Uh , nothing .
- Huh ? - Uh ... Grandma 's spectacles ...
- Did you break them ? - No , no . I didn 't .
Move aside .
You are so useless .
- Four ... - Four ...
- Five ... - Five ...
- Six ... - Six ...
- Seven ... - Seven ...
- Eight ... - Eight ...
- Nine ... - Nine ...
- One ... - One ...
- Zero ... - Zero ...
Ten ... Ten ...
[ GOOD CHILDREN ! ] - Teacher ...
Teacher , if you go on leave so often
it is difficult for us to manage .
Why don 't you take a long break ?
Meanwhile , I 'll appoint someone else here .
No , that won 't be necessary .
Uh ... I 'll continue here .
Please don 't get me wrong ...
We are handling young kids here .
If you could be a little more pleasant in your approach ...
You get what I am saying ?
[ NURSERY RHYMES ]
[ SHALL I DRAW ? ]
[ WHISPERS ] Come , come here ...
[ CRIES ]
- Hello ? - Hey , I am outside .
Am on the second floor .
Is this material for a top ?
- Oh , it goes with this . - This is the dupatta .
OK , how 's this ?
Not bad , I liked the pink one actually .
Ah ! There you are .
What 's going on ?
- Birthday shopping . - Ah .
Can you show me that one , please ?
- How 's it ? - It 's nice .
This color might look better actually .
It 's birthday , after-all !
Any plans after this ?
What plan ? I 've to go home . That 's it .
- Priya ... - What ?
Shall we go somewhere after this ?
No , Vinu .
We can just go and ...
- I am not interested , Vinu . - Why ?
Now you have time , no ?
Huh ?
So , now you have the time to call me and meet me ?
I was in a messed up situation .
What situation ?
Your Grandma 's demise ?
That I can understand . What was the problem before that ?
Before that ... I was not in the right mood .
What ?
So you will call only when you 're in the mood ?
- That 's not what I meant ... - Vinu ...
Calling me and meeting me ... whenever you feel like , won 't work .
Hmm .
It won 't happen again .
If it happens again , you can find another girl .
Can I at least drop you ?
No need . I 'll go with her .
Hmm .
My birthday is on Sunday . I insist you come over .
S ... ure I will .
Come only if you are in the right mood ...
- You need to buy anything ? - Uh , no .
Here you go ...
How are things at home ? Is your Mom fine now ?
- Hmm , she has to . - Hmm .
- Hey ... - Hmm ?
For the other day ...
That was for Rs 1000 .
- 1000 ? - Yeah !
Can I pay the rest next week ?
I am leaving next week .
- Where to ? - Oh , I didn 't tell you , right ?
- Remember , the job I told you about ? - Uh , yeah ...
I decided to take it up .
Should you take up that job after studying D. Pharm ?
We did D.Pharm for sure . But we didn 't learn anything , right ?
Afterall , who is getting a job in their field of studies these days ?
We just want to somehow make it !
- You heard about Sajin ? - What ?
- He 's getting married . - Marriage ? !
You didn 't know ? Don 't you check your Instagram ?
- I 'm not on Insta . - He 's living the life !
I 'll show you .
Here ... that 's the car he bought last week .
Insta is about merely putting up a show .
You and your cynical attitude !
People are moving on with their lives .
We are the only ones stuck here , with no respite .
Aren 't you having dinner ?
Not now .
So you don 't want it at all ?
Can I make some Maggi ( NOODLES ) ?
And who is going to eat ... What I prepared ...
Just eat this .
Unnecessarily troubling others ...
Jimmy ... move aside . I said ... move !
Hope you have lab experience .
Yes , sir . I have completed 100 hours as Pharma Assist .
Hmmn .
Why do you have a career gap of one and a half years ?
Sir , my family situation was such that I needed a job in this town .
So ... I was trying to something here and ...
- In this town ? - Yes , sir . I live here .
Sir , are we hiring for this town ?
No , we haven 't given any advertisement specifying that .
We 're not looking for someone to work in this town .
We are looking for someone who can take up outstation work too .
Uh Sir ...
Your cousin Felin
must 've called you regarding a candidate ? That 's me .
So ? Why are you smiling for that ?
Listen , we work for a corporate company .
When you attend an interview that we conduct
shouldn 't you follow basic etiquette ?
Look at you ... you haven 't even shaved !
My grandmother passed away recently . So , I couldn 't shave ( FOR RELIGIOUS REASONS ) .
Dude , even this sir 's grandmother passed away last week .
Yet , see how he has come ...
Tell me about your family .
Only my mother .
And your father ?
My father died when I was 7 .
What does your mother do ?
She is a school teacher .
Ah ! She managed to teach other kids .
Yet , she couldn 't teach her own kid anything !
These days no one wants to hear anyone 's sentiments .
You may leave now .
What a waste of time !
Send in the next candidate , please !
Hey Vinu ! What 's up ? !
- When did you get here ? - Where were you ?
I stepped out leaving my phone here for charging .
And what 's up ?
- So you 're leaving next week , huh ? - Yes , next Thursday .
Hmm .
Here , have a sweet .
Got some to celebrate getting a job !
Grandma , want one ?
She 's not supposed to have anything sweet .
And what else ?
You know ... here
I am not finding a job ...
- I tried really hard . - OK ...
This place that you 've joined ... You think you could ...
I am going to work in a hotel , man !
That is OK . Anything will do !
I need to get out of here somehow .
Got it ?
Once I am there , may be I can look for something else later .
What about your mother ? Did she agree ?
That 's OK . I 'll get her to agree somehow .
Let me talk to them .
I 'll get it done .
Then shall I get going ?
Stay for a bit ... We can chill in the backyard .
No , I 've some work today .
- You sure ? - Yes .
- So ... I 'll see you then . - OK , then ...
- Hey , listen ... - Yeah ?
We should have a drink and celebrate before I leave , OK ?
Sure ! Let me know when .
- Give me a call . - I will .
[ SHOCKED ]
Hey !
- Nah , he won 't do anything . - Darn !
- Alright , then . - Alright !
[ PHONE BEEPS ]
You started smoking again ?
No .
I got a lighter from your pants ' pocket .
That ... I bought ... for something else .
I forgot what it was for .
What about the job ?
I didn 't get it .
Why ?
They rejected saying that I have a career gap of one and a half years .
I don 't think I 'll find anything here , Mom .
So , you plan to sit at home jobless ?
Jobless ?
I got a job in Salem . You didn 't let me go from here !
That 's because our circumstances was such !
I thought you 'd have understood .
I didn 't know it would take this much time ...
Yeah , they 've stacked and saved for me
all these jobs .
No point saying that .
Everyone goes through the same . You should try somewhere else .
I am not looking here any more , Mom .
Then ?
Shyam has said
he will get me a job .
Where ?
The same hotel that he is going to work at .
We spent so much on your education and you 'll work at a hotel ?
What 's wrong with that ?
Not everyone finds a job in the field they studied .
Vinu , try and stick to one field .
You said you want to do MBBS first and then quit it .
Then you took up D. Pharm .
Do you know how much has been spent on all this ?
Don 't even talk about MBBS now , Mom !
I told you a hundred times that I won 't be able to do it !
You pushed me , saying it was a professional course , it has a certain status ...
Don 't make me say things I don 't want to !
And now I don 't even have a job ... !
Oh !
So that 's also on me !
Asking you to study , you not getting a job ...
- ... it 's all my fault . - Yes , it 's your fault .
Yes ! It 's your fault , Mom !
I wish Dad was around ...
Someone would have understood me .
When your Dad was around
all he made was a huge debt and a bad name !
I still haven 't paid it all back !
Now you go and make some more !
A hotel job ! Is this how I raised you ? !
You are doomed !
You are out to destroy your life , like your father .
I don 't care if it 's destroyed . I 'm leaving this time , Mom .
You 'll go nowhere . I 'd like to see how you leave .
I 'll lock you up !
Aargh ! You have to say something and get me ...
Mom !
I need to talk to you , Mom !
You can 't walk away in the middle of a conversation every single time !
Mom !
[ CRIES ]
It 's OK , dear . Don 't cry ...
That was
by mistake .
How can that happen by mistake ?
That kid 's nose is broken .
She hasn 't stopped crying .
Her parents are on the way .
It was an accident , sir .
I didn 't do it on purpose .
I had told you if you aren 't well , please go on leave .
I am absolutely fine .
If nothing is wrong , then why are you taking so many medicines ?
Anyway , now ... I am in trouble .
If the media comes to know of this , it will cause a huge uproar .
Who knows what type of people the parents are .
Sir , shall I speak to the parents ?
All that is not needed !
Listen , please stay away for a while .
Why did you break it ?
Me ?
No , I did !
Tell me , why did you break it ?
I said ... I did not !
Apart from one of us , who else is there in this house to do it ?
Vinu , I don 't want to fight early morning .
Listen
don 't take out your anger on my phone .
All I have is my phone and bike .
You 're the one fiddling on your phone all the time .
It must have broken .
What is your problem , Mom ?
Is it because you 're having all these medicines ?
It 's OK . It can be fixed .
Good thing Grandma passed away .
- Back then , she bore the brunt of your issues - Hey !
Don 't you dare talk about my mother !
Why not ?
Weren 't you also waiting for her to die anyway ?
Get out of here !
Yeah , that 's the plan . I will leave .
No matter how hard the times were
I never let him feel his father 's absence .
Whatever he wanted
a computer , mobile , a motorcycle
I bought him whatever he wished for .
Yet he ...
It 's the same in all families .
Don 't take these things so seriously .
In my family
there are only problems , always .
Let me write you a medicine . Take it before you sleep .
If you feel like there is a problem ,
or you feel like talking , just come over .
Alright ?
Don 't hurt yourself more by over-thinking it .
Please try to relax first .
Go for a walk . Have an ice cream .
You 'll feel better .
" Like the cloud that eclipses ... "
" ... the time goes on ... "
" ... now yours ! "
" What 's there to say ... I wonder ! "
" In the words ... "
" ... flow a song ! "
" This endless distance from you ... "
" ... goes on endlessly ! "
" Or is it just a dream ? "
" The path the clouds move ... "
" ... can you see it ? "
" ... shall we go ? "
" Oh nightly star ! "
" You shimmer on this night ! "
" Whom do you seek ... "
" Within me ? "
" Whom do you seek ? "
" Oh rhythm of a song ... "
" Oh the nectar-filled flower ... "
" Did your petal brush me ? "
" Or did you touch the spark within me ? "
" A time where time has no limits ... "
" ... is what we seek ! "
" The path the clouds move ... "
" ... can you see it ? "
" ... shall we go then ? "
" Oh nightly star ! "
" You shimmer on this night ! "
" Whom do you seek ... "
" Within me ? "
" Whom do you seek ? "
Mom !
Stop fooling around ... Open the door !
MOM !
[ CRIES ]
Mom ...
Mom !
[ SCREAMS ]
Open the door , Mom !
Mom !
MOM ... Mom ... !
' Intermission '
[ PHONE RINGS ]
Hello ?
Asha ... ?
I called to say ... Vinu is here .
Vinu ... ?
Asha ... ?
- Asha , can you hear me ? - What for ?
I 'll tell you ... when you get here .
Just get an auto-rickshaw and come over .
OK .
He came here early in the morning .
He didn 't tell you while leaving , Asha ?
He says he saw your mother .
That she locked him up in a room .
He 's been blabbering some nonsense .
I think he has a problem .
Remember what I told you then ?
That I saw him coming out of a bar ?
That was in the afternoon .
I know you didn 't take it seriously .
He drinks everyday , Asha .
Look at him .
He looks frail and weak !
I don 't ... interfere in his matters .
You should intervene !
That is the problem .
Hope you haven 't forgotten the past .
We barely made it that time !
If it happens again ...
What should I do now ... ?
I looked after Amma all these years .
And now I must stay home and look after him ?
That 's not what I meant , Asha .
We need to sit him down and explain things to him .
OK .
I 'll talk to him .
No , I don 't think he will listen to us anymore .
He needs to be
counseled .
That 's the only way out .
- But ... - I know the right person .
- But ... - I 'll take care of it .
You have your tea .
Counselling ?
What for ?
So now I am the one who needs to be counseled ? !
- Mr. Madhu ? - Yes .
- Did you 've trouble finding the address ? - No ...
I got a bit confused after getting into this lane .
This is George .
- This is Vinu 's mother . - Ah .
George runs a counseling service in town .
Quick-mind Counseling ...
No ... Freshmind Counseling .
I 've given George an idea ...
- Like I said ... - I get it .
That 's an area we focus on .
Uh ... smoking addiction ... alcoholism .
Let 's try , Sir .
... and then ...
- ... the door shut . - Hmm .
And then it got locked .
- And then I saw ... - Hmm .
Then
how did the door open finally ?
After a while it opened by itself .
And ?
And then I stepped out .
OK ...
And there was no one there .
And then when I went to Amma 's room ...
- ... she was also not there . - Oh , is it ?
That 's when I went to my Dad 's brother 's house .
Why do you think you felt these things ?
Feeling ?
- I am telling you what I saw . - That 's what ...
Why do you think you saw these things ?
Well ... what can I say ...
No no ... relax . Don 't get tensed .
Relax yourself and answer .
I am relaxed .
But you aren 't understanding what I am saying .
- No , I get it . - What ?
I got it . I was just ... asking .
Uh ... Vinu ...
Do you drink ?
Drinking is not a bad thing .
Do you ?
I mean , last night or evening
did you have a drink ?
I didn 't .
And smoking ?
Yes .
Cigarettes ?
So , when you got stressed
did you smoke something else other than cigarettes ?
Listen , you can trust me . Be comfortable .
I 've been through all these things .
- No , I didn 't . - Come on , be open .
NO !
Hmm .
Isn 't this rolling paper ?
This right here ?
Come on .
Why are you staring at me like that ?
Say something . Be comfortable .
You should leave .
Don 't say that !
- Leave . - See ...
You ... you relax a bit .
I am not here to trouble you .
Leave .
Please try to understand .
Whatever is on your mind ... let it come out .
- Just leave . - See , I will help you .
I am fine . Please leave .
I know you 're fine . I know that .
There is no problem . I know ... I know .
So ...
So what happened yesterday ...
- ... that feeling ... - Just leave , Sir .
OK .
Has he created such issues before ?
Not really ...
When he was in college ... he used to get drunk and ...
He was always a headache for us .
The boy was enrolled in MBBS .
Look at him now .
- Oh , what happened ? - He wouldn 't attend classes .
He wouldn 't answer calls .
He wouldn 't come home .
You know what we heard when we went to check ?
It seems he hadn 't stepped out of his room for 4-5 days .
All he did was drink and smoke .
His mind ... is completely troubled .
I think he hasn 't slept for at least three days .
Any human who hasn 't slept in 48 hours could hallucinate .
He will imagine visuals and sounds .
That can be dangerous .
And if his family history is as you say
his mother 's issues , grandmother 's ...
This could be an extension of that .
Should we take him to a doctor ?
Not yet , Sir .
Let me try again .
We 'll take a call after that .
I 'll come again tomorrow .
OK .
[ SOUNDS FROM THE TV ]
There was some sound there . Some sound ...
- I 'll check . - No ...
There is no one there , Vinu .
It was a loud sound ! And you didn 't hear anything ?
No , I didn 't .
So , I am the one hearing these voices now ... ?
Please try to sleep ...
- Everything will be fine . - What will be fine ? !
Huh ?
I am the one listening to it all !
Hi , teacher ..
How are you ? All good ?
Yes .
Aren 't you working today ?
- I am on leave . - Ah !
Isn 't your son around ? Haven 't seen him in a while ...
Uh , hmm .
He is inside .
- Asha ? - Yes ...
Please go in .
Dr. Beena ... ?
Doctor Beena got transferred .
Please have a seat .
Alright , tell me . What 's the problem ?
Sir ...
- No one is home . - Where did they go ?
Don 't know . The teacher left early . Later I saw the boy also leave .
Oh .
Sir ...
Don 't stand there alone for a long time .
Why ?
Something about that house isn 't right .
What did you say about that house ?
- Who is it ? - He came to visit the teacher .
They 've gone out .
Are you a relative ?
No , I am here to meet her son .
Oh , alright .
Uh , what were you saying about that house ?
That ... nothing else ...
There is something wrong with that house , sir .
Everyone who lived there has faced some problem .
Isn 't it their own house ?
No ! They 're on rent .
We never go there .
But ... why ?
A man who was living there , hanged himself to death .
He did not die alone . Poor thing ...
He poisoned his wife and kid . They too died .
We came to know only after 5-6 days , when it started stinking ...
Have you gone inside ? The room in front of the entrance .
- That 's where he ... - Nah !
- That 's where the wife and the kid lay . - No , that 's where he was .
- He was in the next room ! - Fine ... wherever then .
When was this ?
That must 've been about ...
- ... 6-7 years back , right ? - Yeah .
Yeah , about 6-7 years back .
Then , the house remained locked for 2-3 years .
And later they started renting it out .
But none of the tenants would stay long .
2-3 months at the most .
- The last person was a banker , right ? - Right .
- What was his name ? - Anand ?
Correct ! Anand .
He was a really nice man .
One day , he too tried to hang himself .
But luckily , he didn 't die ! He made it alive .
Hello ?
Is this George ? I am Vinu 's mother .
Ah , tell me Ma 'am .
You said you 'll come today .
When will you be coming ?
Uh , that ... Madam ... uh ...
I am not in town .
I was about to call Mr. Madhu .
Last night
he behaved in a completely bizarre way with me .
Can you do something ?
I can bring him there , if you 'd prefer that .
Uh , no . That 's not needed .
Let me call you once I am free .
Alright .
Any updates on my case ?
- What case ? - The job ?
Oh , yes . I will talk to them , man .
You forgot about it ?
No man ! Let me get there .
I 'll set you up .
- Mix some water too . - I need only soda .
Here we go . Come on , let 's raise a toast !
Cheers ... Cheers ...
Cheers !
Go for it , man !
Come on !
Catch it !
Come here , let me pour you another one .
Where ... where is the stuff ?
Hey ! Come on !
Here you go ...
Hmm .
Why are you standing aside ? Come here . Let 's dance !
Dance !
Here !
You come here ...
[ MUMBLES SOMETHING ]
Hey , look !
Hey .. Hey ...
That 's OK , no problem ! Don 't worry !
No problem !
I 'll do it . Step aside .
Careful with your hands .
Nobody should cut their hands , guys ! Blood should not be spilt !
Hey ..
I need to take a leak .
- What ? - I need to pee .
- Go inside ... - Inside ?
Yeah , use the washroom .
Yeah , that way .
Go in and take a right .
[ SHRIEKS ]
What is it ?
- Hey , what happened ? - Nothing .
What is it !
Hey ... I will
clean it . - No , it 's OK .
- Come ... - I suddenly ...
Come ... come ...
Come ...
Take him .
Sit , it 's alright .
Mom ...
Can I sleep with you tonight ?
I don 't want to sleep in my room .
- Why aren 't you answering the call ? - It 's her .
I told you ... it 's that lady .
Whatever it is , just answer .
What if it 's an emergency ?
No . It is not necessary .
Anyway , I am going call Mr. Madhu and tell him .
- Is it because you are scared ? - Not at all ...
Not because I 'm scared .
Just because someone said something , don 't leave the case .
Find out if there is any truth in what they are saying .
After that you can take a call , right ?
- You 're Mr Rajan ? - Yes ...
I called you in the morning to ask about your house .
I don 't have anything other than what I said over the phone .
You needn 't have come .
- Have a seat . - Thanks .
Is the house for you or are you a broker ?
Sir ... it is for a friend of mine .
I thought I 'll just enquire .
The house is on sale .
I 've rented it out now .
Sir ... I came to ask something else too .
In that house
I heard that some tragedy had happened .
A family living there ... did something ...
Not just ' some family ' .
That was my son and his family ...
You came to ask that ?
Sorry , sir , I didn 't know that .
He was in some sort of a problem and ...
Right ?
He did not have any problem ...
She was the problem !
His wife .
After they got married , they built the house and moved in .
She was the first one who said that the house had some problem .
Later she started saying that my son was mentally ill .
Saying it repeatedly , she eventually made him completely crazy
and made him do unspeakable things .
If the townsfolk are right
he poisoned his wife and child and died by hanging himself .
It 's now a story that people like you can talk about .
Has no one ever died in your house ?
Haven 't you continued staying there ?
Isn 't it just a house ?
Made of stones , mud , cement , and wood ...
- Is this Mr. Anand 's house ? - Yes , who is it ?
- Is he here ? - Yes .
- Come in . - OK .
Sleeplessness was his main problem .
The doctor said it was due to stress .
He asked me to serve food and went into his room ...
When I went in ... I saw him hanging ...
Because I saw him on time , he could be saved .
But this is his condition since then .
And ...
He kept saying he saw someone and heard some things in that house .
Apart from both of us
there was no one there .
But ...
If you watch closely
you can see someone else too there , he says .
Why did you want to meet so urgently ?
Hmm ?
Can we go somewhere ?
Go ... ? Where ?
Somewhere far away .
You wanted to meet so urgently to say this ?
Not that .
Then ?
- Please take what I am saying seriously , OK ? - Okay .
Tell me .
I told you about getting locked up in the room , right ?
- And that my phone was broken ? - Yeah ?
That wasn 't Amma .
Then ?
I don 't know .
There is something there .
What thing ?
Vinu ...
You know ... I haven 't slept in 4 days .
I ...
When I think of something ...
I can 't understand what is happening to me .
I am ...
And Mom has arranged some guy to counsel me ...
- Counseling ? - Yeah ! Counseling .
She got a counselor saying I 've a problem .
Vinu ...
Why didn 't you tell me this sooner ?
Huh ?
I can 't continue in that house , Priya .
- Can we go somewhere ? - Vinu ...
If you spring this on me all of a sudden ...
You do one thing ...
Go home and get some sleep .
Get some rest .
Uh ...
What did the counselor say ?
Forget it . It 's OK .
Vinu ...
- Sorry , brother ! - Get lost !
Hey move ! Get away .
Catch him !
The fellow is crazy !
Let go off me !
I 'll kick the life out of him !
Hey ... hey ...
Hey , stop it . Don 't kick .
Don 't do that . Get him away , guys .
Pin him down .
- I 'll kick him ! - Please leave ...
- Enough ... move aside ! - He is crazy !
Asha , if you had been more careful about him
this wouldn 't have happened .
No point in saying it now .
He needs proper rest , Asha .
I 'll look after him .
I 'll ensure that my son doesn 't go anywhere .
That is not what I meant !
He needs proper institutional rest .
That includes therapy and medication .
Look at him , Asha .
He is ruining himself .
Until now , only we knew about it .
Now he is a nuisance for others too .
There isn 't much to think now . There is a hospital nearby .
You don 't need to worry , Asha . I 'll manage .
- Hello ? - Sir ... Regarding Vinu 's case
I feel there seems to be some truth in what he was saying .
When I enquired about that house ,
I learnt that the house has some problems .
The problem is not with the house ...
It 's with him .
Today he got into a fight at the bar .
I got him home somehow .
Sir , can I just speak to him once ?
No , George . That is not required .
I don 't think this can be fixed with counseling .
We are taking him to a hospital tomorrow .
Sir , I just want to talk to him once .
No , George .
Mental hospitals are the best remedy for mad people .
I 'll call you later .
Eat your food .
I am not hungry .
Your tiredness will wear off only if you eat .
Then you 'll have sound sleep .
Tomorrow morning , everything will be fine .
Don 't be scared .
Do you know what I am scared of , Mom ?
The fear of our loved ones not understanding us .
In everyone 's eyes , I am
I am someone with a problem .
Do I have any problem , Mom ?
Don 't cry , Mom .
Are you crying because of me ?
I won 't hurt you again .
Mom ...
No one understands me , Mom .
You should stand by me , Mom .
Don 't you understand ... ?
Don 't you see me ?
Who is all this for ?
What have I lived all my life for ?
In my life
I 've made a number of mistakes .
I don 't want you to repeat those mistakes ... that 's why ...
I thought you had something against me ...
Don 't cry , Mom ...
Don 't cry , Mom .
Don 't cry .
Mom ...
It 's OK .
Mom !
What is it , Vinu ? What ?
- The glass moved ... - What ?
- Huh ? - Yeah !
- What is it ? - [ CLICKS TONGUE ]
[ BOTH SCREAM ]
Mom ! MOM !
- Where 's your phone ? - Uh ?
Where is your phone ?
No . I don 't have the phone .
[ MUFFLED SCREAM ]
[ INAUDIBLE ]
[ SHRIEKS IN FEAR ]
Front door ... front door !
Where is the key ?
On top of the fridge .
Don 't Vinu ...
[ CRIES ]
Look at me ...
Give me the keys .
Vinu , give me the keys !
Give it !
Give !
[ GASPS ]
I don 't believe in these things .
They wanted to move out . Fine , OK !
This is all we can do .
- These are personal experiences of people . - Hmnn .
We should help them in the way we can .
But if we start thinking like that , which house can we live in ?
- Every house will have its own problems . - Hmnn .
In any case , what we wished for has happened .
- The mother and the son have reconciled . - [ SMILES ]
Other than that , there is no point in us overthinking this
and getting trapped in this house !
- Right ? - Right .
What are you thinking , Son ?
Nothing .
You said you will tell me
everything from now on .
I was thinking
about the people who 'll live here next .
[ SIGHS ]